[instrumental music]
Jess, this is gonna be great.
The boys' first night in
their new beds, golden footage.
Yeah, I can see it now,
Nicky and Alex Katsopolis
are...the young
and the tired.
Alright, here we go.
Lights, camera..
...cuteness.
Cuteness.
Either they're gone,
or I left the lens cap on.
Both.
[children laughing]
(child #1)
'Mommy.'
Jess.
[children laughing]
Look under the covers.
Two biggest
bedbugs I ever saw.
- We found you.
- 'Hey!'
Hi, big daddy.
Don't "big daddy" me.
You are supposed to
be in your own beds.
That's right.
You guys go in your own bed.
No. Big bed.
No big bed.
You go in your bed.
- No. Big bed.
- Big bed.
Hey. No, I'm not kidding.
Get out of there.
[children laughing]
Alright, Beck, cover me.
I'm going in.
- Alright.
- Look out!
I'll head 'em off at the pass.
[theme music]
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
♪ Ah-h-h ♪
♪ Whatever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milkman the paperboy ♪
♪ Evenin' TV ♪
♪ Ah-h-h ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold on to ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Everywhere you go ♪
♪ There's a face ♪
♪ Of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waitin' ♪
♪ To carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Do be do ba ba da ♪♪
[instrumental music]
Don't forget this.
Goodbye, Danielle.
Goodbye, Michelle.
I can't believe camp
is over tomorrow.
Thanks for teaching
me how to power-spit.
Goodbye, Denise.
I'm gonna miss
you so much.
But I live right
down the block.
I know, but now
we can't scratch
each other's
mosquito bites.
Ah-h-h.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Michelle,
have you said goodbye
to all your
chickadee bunkmates?
Not yet. There's
still just one more.
Goodbye, Gilbert.
I'd write you every day
but you'd just eat the paper.
I know how you feel, kid.
I made a few good friends
myself this summer.
David, Billy
Sean, Gregg.
Good thing I played hard-to-get.
Okay, girls.
Attention, attention.
Lights out in
five minutes.
It's very important
to get plenty of sleep
last night of camp.
So we won't be tired tomorrow?
So us counselors
can party tonight.
(both)
Whatcha!
Alright.
[blows whistle]
Speed it up,
you little twerpcicles.
Better get back
to your cabin, blondie.
Isn't it past your bedtime too?
You know, Kimmy, you could use
a little beauty rest yourself.
About a year should
bring you up to a yuck.
[all laughing]
[knocking on door]
Male counselor
entering chickadee bunk.
- Hi, Steve.
- Hey.
D.J., your husband's here.
He's not my husband.
Not yet.
(all)
Oo-o-oh!
Steve, it's
the last night
and you promised
to tell us a story
about that maniac guy.
Well, I don't know, guys.
It's pretty scary.
You should probably all
go to the bathroom first.
(all)
No. Come on.
Tell us. You promised.
Okay, alright,
I'll tell it.
[laughing maniacally]
It was a dark..
...and stormy night.
Old man Cropsy
looked out the window
and saw a bulldozer bearing down
on his cabin. Oh, no!
[rattling]
He ran down to stop it
but his foot got caught
in the broken floorboard!
The thunder was so loud..
...that nobody could
hear Cropsy scream.
[screaming]
[all gasp]
That bulldozer buried him alive
'under a pile
of rubble and mud.'
You know what they built
right where Cropsy's cabin was?
This camp!
[all gasp]
So now
whenever it rains..
...out of the slimy
sludge it comes
just looking for
scared little campers.
Half man..
...half mud.
[intense music]
The Cropsy maniac!
[kids screaming]
[screaming continues]
Gee, I hope I
didn't scare anybody.
Not me.
I was just looking for a sock.
♪ I couldn't sleep
at all last night ♪
♪ Turned my pillow upside-down ♪
♪ Doo doo do-doo-do ♪
♪ I never, never did before ♪
♪ Because I was
tossin' and turnin' ♪
♪ Turnin' and tossin' ♪
♪ A-tossin' and turnin'
all night ♪♪
[children laughing]
(Jesse)
'Have mercy.'
[honking]
Hey, Jess, you
look kinda tired.
- Rough night last night, huh?
- Yeah.
The twins,
they wouldn't sleep
in their new beds.
So they had to sleep with us.
You ever spend a whole night
with a toe in your ear?
No, not someone else's.
How's the welcome-home
meal coming?
Oh, perfect. I've made
all the girls' favorites.
'They'll love it.'
Oh, I miss those girls so much.
I must've read Michelle's
postcard a hundred times.
"Dear family,
I have to write this
"or I can't go to lunch.
Love, Michelle."
[crying]
That munchkin.
It's the first time I got
through it without crying.
What are you, a stone?
They're back!
[indistinct shouting]
A-a-ah!
- He-e-ey!
- He-e-ey! You guys are back.
- Hey, you guys.
Hey! Hi!
- Hi!
- Guys.
Alright, girls,
tell us all about camp.
- Oh, it was so great.
- It was the best.
[indistinct chattering]
We went swimming,
and fishing, and canoeing.
- It was great.
- It was awesome.
Maybe I'll just send
for the transcripts.
Nicky, Alex, I made you guys
a present in arts and crafts.
Here's a lion for Nicky
''cause that's his
favorite animal'
and a lion for Alex
'cause that's all they
taught us how to make.
Alright you guys, what
do you say to Michelle?
- Grr, grr, grr.
- Grr-r-r.
That is Lionese for
thank you very much.
Alright beastie boys, even
kings of the jungle need a nap
so let's get you
into those new beds.
- Big bed.
No, not the big bed,
your own bed.
- No, big bed.
- No.
- Big bed.
- Those new beds are a big hit.
Uh, speaking of big hits, you
girls better brace yourselves
for the ultimate in
homecoming celebrations.
And hold on to your knapsacks
because for lunch I've
made all your favorites.
You mean, chipped
beef and bug juice?
We love that stuff.
Guys, Joey can't make that.
That's camp food.
Besides, no one can
make it like Greasy Abe.
That's funny, I don't remember
any Greasy Abe in the brochure.
What's important is
that we're all together
and we're all having a great
time. Right, munchkin?
Uncle Jesse, could you please
not call me munchkin anymore?
Why? I-I've called
you munchkin for years.
You've been my
munchkin since day one.
Yeah, but everybody at
camp calls me Trailmix.
Trailmix.
It's cute..
...if you're a raisin.
What was that,
Uncle Jessy?
Oh, I said, it's,
uh, it's amazin'
how cute that
name actually is.
Uh, would you
guys excuse me?
I've got to
write a letter to
David, Billy
Sean and Gregg.
Those sound suspiciously
like boys' names.
By Jove, I think you've
cracked the code, guv'nor!
Well, I have
to go call Steve.
This is the longest we've
been apart all summer.
W-wait a second, girls, this is
the part where we're supposed to
you know, talk and-and rebond
and say how much
we missed each other.
Well, dad, we missed
you too, but can we do
that bonding stuff later?
Yeah, I gotta go unpack and see
if my clothes still
smell like camp.
♪ We love Camp Lakota ♪
♪ Lakota Lakota ♪
♪ The camp that we love is ♪
♪ Did we mention that we love ♪
♪ Lakota ♪♪
I don't get it.
When I was a kid and I came back
from Camp Meadowlark
I couldn't wait to be home.
I was so happy.
I kissed my parents.
I-I-I kissed my bed.
I kissed the floor.
Danny, it was a day camp.
Yeah, but it was
a very long day.
Hey, Steph,
do you have those
plastic sandals
I lent you?
No, but I know where they are.
Great! Where are they?
At the bottom of the lake.
I told you
they wouldn't fit.
It's not my fault
you have big feet.
- Well, you should--
- Well, you should have known--
[indistinct chattering]
Quiet! You're scaring Gilbert.
Sorry, Michelle.
We didn't mean to scare..
(both)
Gilbert?
Floppy-eared, sniffle-nosed,
carrot-breath Gilbert?
Please. He's very
sensitive about his breath.
Michelle, you were supposed
to let him go at the camp.
I tried, but he didn't want to.
It was his decision.
Oh, come on.
It's true, I asked him if he
wanted to go back to the woods
and he went..
Yo, yo, yo. Laundry patrol.
Alright, I've been
waiting for three weeks
to attack these
stubborn grass stains.
Girls, I've missed you so much.
We have so much
catching up to do.
Alright, we've
got your darks.
We've got your lights.
We've got..
...a rabbit.
Why are you holding a rabbit?
'Cause he likes to be held.
His name is Gilbert.
He had a broken leg
when we found him.
But we nursed him back
to health and Michelle
was supposed to set
him free in the woods.
Way to go, Trailmix.
[knocking on door]
Male counselor entering
chickadee bedroom.
- Steve.
- Hi, Steve.
Uh, Steve, sorry to
break up the reunion
but you guys
just got home.
Don't you wanna see your folks?
Oh, I saw them already.
They look pretty
much the same.
Oh, hey, Gilbert.
How's it twitchin'?
Michelle, honey.
Look, I'm sorry, but you
know Gilbert can't stay here.
- He belongs with his friends.
- But I am his friend.
No, you know what I mean.
I mean-I mean his forest friends
you know the ones with,
with fur and four legs
who breed indiscriminately.
Honey, you know
where he belongs
and it's not
in a gym bag.
I know, dad.
Gilbert, you need to go home.
I'll run the little
fur-ball back up to camp.
Oh, I'll go with you.
- Me too.
- Me three.
Wait a minute.
You guys just got home.
Oh, come on, dad, please.
It's just an hour away.
- Please, please..
- Oh, come on..
Okay, okay, you can go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
This is great. We were so
bummed out about leaving camp.
But now we can go back.
Let's move it.
- See ya.
- Bye.
Hey, when you guys come back,
we're gonna have some
real quality time
together, okay?
[girls singing]
♪ The camp that we love is.. ♪♪
Welcome home, girls.
[instrumental music]
[thunder rumbling]
Well, we're wet,
but we're back.
It looks so weird in here.
Everything looks so different.
Well, that's because
we're not here anymore.
Sure feels like we're here.
Fine, we're here.
Let's just dump
the bunny and split.
[thunder rumbling]
Uh, guys, somebody is missing.
Gilbert chewed
right through the box.
Boy, isn't that
just like a rabbit?
I never got to say goodbye.
Steve, we have a problem.
Gilbert escaped.
Oh, Michelle,
I'm really sorry
but I'm afraid we've
got a bigger problem now.
My car is stuck in
a huge, slimy mud puddle.
Oh, no, he's out there!
Who's out there?
Hello! Mud?
Cropsy maniac, remember?
Michelle, that's
just a story.
[thunder rumbling]
I hope Cropsy knows that.
[intense music]
[instrumental music]
(Jesse)
'Okay, come on,
now, now, let's, uh'
let's get the boys
to S-L-E-E-P.
So we can get
the H-E-C-K O-U-T.
Okay, but F-I-R-S-T
W-E S-H-O-U-L-D.
Hold on.
Let me get a crayon.
Honey, never mind. Let's just
get on with it. I'm exhausted.
Me too. Okay, come on.
Let's go to sleep, now.
We're gonna go sleep in
our racecar beds, okay?
And we're gonna
race on to sleep.
Vroom vroom vroom.
[chuckles]
Say, goodnight, daddy.
- Goodnight, daddy.
- Goodnight, Nicky.
Goodnight.
Okay, say
goodnight, mommy.
Goodnight, mommy.
Say, goodnight, Alex.
- Goodnight, Alex.
- 'Very good.'
Now, here we go, we're
gonna sleep in our new beds.
- Bad bed.
- Yucky bed.
No, no, no,
it's not yucky bed.
It's nice bed.
Comfy bed.
Expensive bed.
Jess, let's face it,
we're gonna be sleeping
like this for
the rest of our lives.
Don't worry, Beck.
They'll be out pretty soon.
I'm fried myself.
Me too.
[instrumental music]
[music continues]
[switch clicks]
Shh.
Goodnight, buddy.
Goodnight, brother.
[thunder rumbling]
Whoa.
Stephanie, when is D.J.
and Steve coming back?
As soon as they push
the car out of the mud.
What if they bump
into you-know-who?
- Cropsy?
- Shh!
Michelle, there
is no Cropsy maniac.
That's just a story
that counselors tell kids
to shut them up
so they can go make out.
Oh.
[thunder rumbling]
[intense music]
[door creaking]
Please be D.J.
Please be D.J. Please be D.J.
D.J.
Poor little Michelle thought
you were the Cropsy maniac.
How cute.
You can take
your fingernails
out of my arm
now, Steph.
[grunts]
[thunder rumbling]
[electricity buzzing]
The light.
Okay, that's it.
Where's my coat?
Taxi.
Steph, don't worry. Steve's
calling for help right now.
- No, he's not.
- Ah!
- Don't do that.
- I'm sorry.
I came in the back door.
Look, the storm blew
all the phone lines down.
[rustling]
[groaning]
- What was that?
- It was probably just the wind.
Just the wind?
It's never just the wind!
Hey, I-I think
somebody's out there.
It's Cropsy!
I have an idea. Ready?
- Yeah.
- Grab on.
Okay.
Don't worry,
girls, I was on
the wrestling team
for two years.
[door creaking]
Uh...three years
would've been better.
[door creaking]
[all screaming]
Run for it, girls!
[grunting]
[screaming continues]
Hold on, girls,
girls, it's dad.
It's me!
It's me.
[man grunting]
Dad, Steve just captured
the Cropsy maniac.
Oh, no.
Steve, Steve. Steve!
I think you captured
the wrong maniac.
Huh?
Oh, hey, Joey.
How's it going?
He fell in the mud.
Oxygen.
Brain, everything
getting dark.
Oh, sorry.
Joey, are you okay?
(Joey)
'Mommy? I'm fine, mommy.'
Girls, are you guys okay?
Yeah, we're fine, dad.
What are you doing here?
Well, I guess
you know that, uh..
...you left
something at home.
Here you go, sweetheart.
Gilbert.
Hey, the power is back on.
And look, the rain's
letting up.
Let's get out of here.
Fast.
Why did we come back here?
I think you were thinking that
this was a place that you loved.
But then when you came
back here you realized
it wasn't the same and you're
kind of let down, huh?
'You know what it's like?'
It's like when you
go to the movies
when the show is over
you know the magic's all gone.
All that's left is
just a big empty room
with a, with
a sticky floor.
So, this is it.
Summer is really over.
Come on, Gilbert,
back to the forest.
Time for you to go home.
Honey, it's time for
all of us to go home.
Come on, buddy.
[instrumental music]
Okay, some more fresh
s'mores hot out of the fire.
Okay. Careful, Michelle, okay?
They're still hot.
Ooh, these are hot.
Yeah, well, I bet Greasy Abe
never made s'mores like these.
Okay, here we go.
Drinks for everybody.
[all cheering]
Now, where the heck
are those s'mores, huh?
- Whoa!
[all laughing]
I think I just found
them. Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
[all laughing]
Ow!
- Get down. Get down.
- Ow! Ow! Ow!
[all laughing]
Foam on the landing strip.
Oh!
[all laughing]
I can't resist.
(Joey)
'What? What? What?'
- 'You know what we need now?'
- 'What?'
- Six spoons, that's--
- Oh, no!
- Oh.
- Here, let me, uh..
Let me, uh, let me..
You know what?
You better do this.
Oh, okay, okay, I agree.
You know,
we had fun at camp..
...but we really
missed you guys.
[instrumental music]
You mean it?
You're really happy to be home?
Of course, we are.
We didn't hurt your feelings
talking about camp and all?
- No.
- No, no, no.
We're really sorry.
Ah-h-h.
- Thanks, dad.
- Don't hug back there.
You might..
[indistinct chattering]
It's nice to have
you back, Trailmix.
Uncle Jesse,
if it's okay
could you call
me munchkin again?
Okay, munchkin again.
Uncle Jesse.
I love you, munchkin.
Okay, who, uh, who
wants something to drink?
- Oh, I do.
- I do.
- 'There you go.'
- 'Thank you.'
(Jesse)
'Beck, you want some?'
Hey, hey, hey, calm it!
Oh, quit it. There's
a man under these pants.
[barking]
[all laughing]
I'm not having a good day.
[instrumental music]
♪ Ah ah ah ah ♪
[theme music]
♪ Do be do ba ba da ♪♪